All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, after taming the terrors of the deep, they have finally made their way to Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level.
Listen up, guys!
Let's go!
How about I give you an option?
Enlist under our banner as members of the new Fishman Pirates.
Or else...
Or else meaning we sink you right now!
Yeah, right, you wish!
Stupid!
Here goes...
Coo-de-burst!
This bubble...
It's a double structure!
We're about to run into another bubble!
You guys ready?
Water?
This current is really strong!
Crap!
Four of us can't swim!
Come on!
Reach!
Nami!
Robin!
Dammit!
I can't resist the current!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
This is a coral apartment complex.
The dorms are at the very bottom, so rinse cheap.
The top floor is the most expensive because it gets natural light.
It's the surface!
We made it!
Hey!
K-me!
Hey, guys!
Huh?
Finally!
I found my all blue after all these years!
Interesting.
So Straw Hat finally made it to our turf, did he?
Good for him.
Well, what are we gonna do about it, boss?
I want you to bring him here.
And quickly.
Excitement Blowout!
Sanji's life under threat!
The Straw Hats are human, they can't breathe down here.
Assuming they're still alive, there aren't many places they can go.
Guess we should head for town, huh?
No.
Wherever they are, they can't hide from Lord.
Well, great.
Okay, now what should I do?
It's hard to believe I'm so far under water.
Huh?
Super...
Landing.
Hey, Nami.
Whew, glad you made it out okay.
Yeah? No thanks to you!
You almost gave me a heart attack, you big dummy!
Robin!
Robin.
Hey.
Nami?
You alright?
Is this...
Fishman Island?
Yeah, probably.
Frankie's scouting out the area to figure that out.
Hmm? Back in the land of the living?
So it seems.
Find anyone else?
Nope.
They're all thrown in different directions.
Geez.
We just got back together again, too.
Eh, we'll find them sooner or later.
They're tough suckers, so I'm sure they're doing fine wherever they are.
He does have a point.
No offense to the crew, but I'm more worried about the sunny.
I'm hoping the locals might have heard some news about our big crash.
I saw a town right around the corner.
Huh?
Ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!!
Conti!?
Alright, here I come!
This is it!
This is my new.
Home!
usa.
He isn't spewing blood everywhere, so I guess he's better now.
I don't get it.
This sucks. I want to swim, too.
You can. All we have to do is get you a bubble.
Oh, really?
Uh-huh. We can have one made in the city. Sound good?
Yeah!
This is a lucky break.
If he had a nosebleed now, we wouldn't be able to do a transfusion.
Sanji's blood type is rare, and we're all out.
What? That sounds like seriously bad news.
Hey, Kami?
Huh?
While I'm here, there's somebody I'd really like to see if we can find them somehow.
Oh? Don't tell me. The Mermaid Princess?
Nope. It's Jinbei.
They call him Boss down here.
Wait. When you say Jinbei, you're talking about the Warlord Jinbei?
Or, I mean, former Warlord, since he resigned after the whole war thing.
Yeah. He's a good friend of mine.
Huh? Him and the Pirate Empress?
You make some weird friends when we're not around.
When Ace died two years ago, I had a tough time pulling it together.
In fact, I doubt I'd even be here right now, if it wasn't for his help.
I've had enough of your nonsense!
Boy, you can't see a thing. You're blind.
What's gone may be gone, but you still have something left in this world to treasure, don't you?
I still have my crew!
I can't wait to talk to him again!
See you on Fishman Island in two years! Be sure to bring your entire crew along! I look forward to meeting everyone!
He said to meet here, and there's no way I'm gonna let him down!
Now that you mention it, I heard he went to Marineford with you when you rang that bell and everyone got all worked up!
Yahoo!
You know where we can find him?
Well, it's kind of tricky, because Boss doesn't exactly live on the island with everyone else.
Huh?
Since he resigned from the Warlords, they have to treat him like a normal pirate again.
That means all the Fishman Pirates can't stay in the city anymore, so they found a new place to live.
It's not too far from here, but that's where you'll have to go if you want to see him.
What? That sounds like a pain. This place has some dumb rules.
I know it seems weird, but even though we're all the way down here, the War of the Best ended up affecting us, too.
Kamee! Kamee! Kamee! Kamee! Kamee! Kamee!
Huh?
There's a big ship coming!
Kamee! It's a ship from the palace!
Yeah, but maybe nobody's on it.
Don't be stupid. Of course someone is.
So did you see somebody on the ship or not?
No, not yet.
But it was for sure the royal family ship. They don't usually come around here.
Maybe they've come here to arrest Luffy because he didn't enter the city the right way.
So what if they do?
Huh?
You guys had better hide before they get here.
Sanji, quick, this way.
Yeah!
She's right. That ship's the royal gondola.
I thought so.
I knew.
Maybe.
Totally. So what?
Even so, I doubt anyone from the royal family is actually riding on it.
This corner of the island's sort of out of the way for them, so they don't usually bother.
Attention, all citizens! The three Neptune brothers have arrived!
Greetings, ladies of the cove. I hope that you can answer an inquiry of mine.
Ahh! The princess are here!
That's me! Anything!
That princess?
Sanji, no!
Hide here and stay still.
What is this feeling? Marshmallow, maybe?
No, it's too big for that. But it has such a sweet smell. Intoxicating like some forbidden fruit. Yet too soft to be a melon. Too warm.
Hey, what are...
Ahh!
I received a report that someone entered the city illegally. Have they come by here, perhaps?
If they have, and you've seen them, be sure to tell me if I saw Latina!
Mumbo, mumbo, shiki shiki moonfish, why we gotta do this? Let's party with the ladies!
I'm sorry, but we haven't seen anyone here.
They sound like common thugs. Are they really that important?
Surely they don't demand the attention of princes such as you.
Perhaps. We have yet to ascertain their identities, so it may be too early to say just yet.
He doesn't know! Latina!
Who cares? Let's dance! Yay! Ain't nobody nothing about nobody!
What's all this commotion?
Oh man, it's the princess from Neptune's army!
What are they doing here? What a pain in the ass.
Now what?
Let's see how it plays out.
Mumbo, mumbo, shiki!
Ah, I see. Well, I thank you all. We shall search elsewhere.
Forgive me for interrupting your leisure.
We'll dance again sometime!
And away we go! Latina!
Bye-bye!
Perhaps the border guards were just seeing things!
They're leaving...
So soft...
And...
Pink...
Soft...
Squishy...
Fuffy!
Ooh, ooh, what is that?
Aw, crap, Sanji!
Oh, what did I do?
That was too much blood! He needs help now!
He's done for! All that pent-up lust let loose in one shot!
Sanji!
Wait, no mistaking it.
That's the pirate's straw hat Luffy.
Mom-o-nights, go!
Yes, sir!
What a pain!
Everything here looks the same.
I could be walking in circles for all I know.
You're Roro Noah Zoro from the Straw Hat Pirates, right?
Yeah, so what if I am?
Well, look at that. How convenient.
I don't know, the gods are gonna catch him first.
Our orders are clear, but we don't want to start crap with the Neptune army.
Wait, hold on a second, please!
We don't want to fight! We can sort out our crimes later!
But right now there's an emergency!
Our friend has lost a lot of blood and we need a donor, quick!
If you leave him here or throw him in jail, he'll be dead within an hour!
His blood type is SRH negative.
I know it's rare, but does someone here have it? Anyone?
Fishmen and humans do have the same kind of blood, don't they?
Chopper chin.
We don't have time! Guys, this is serious!
Sanchi, we are not losing you over this!
Please, I'm begging you! Whatever it takes!
I can't let my friend die!
Chopper chin, I'm sorry.
Fishmen and humans do have the same kind of blood, but the situation is complicated.
The thing is...
Hammo, Hammo, Hammo, Hammo!
Get a load of these humans!
You really are stupid, aren't you?
Weren't you a big enough jerk the last time we met?
His name is Hammond, sir. He's from the Fishmen District.
Hammo, Hammo, Hammo!
You're not getting a damn drop from anybody on this island!
Why would we share our blood with disgusting creatures like you?
Humans aren't worth a thing down here!
And even if someone did help you, decent fishmen like us who hate humans would make sure they were punished for it.
Punished?
He can bleed out right here for all I care. Many fishmen would happily watch him die.
There's a law for this, you know. One we've followed for a long time.
Fishmen are forbidden to share blood with humans no matter what.
That law sucks!
Don't blame me for it.
After all, it was humans who set the rule in the first place.
Our blood may be the same, but for ages you've treated us like monsters or worse, like animals.
Your blood was too good for us!
In fact, that's why Fisher Tiger, the hero of this island, died.
He said that name once before.
He fought to free slaves of all races, and when that battle took its toll on his body, when he lied bloody and battered, not a single human would offer their blood to return his kindness.
A transfusion would have saved him, but because of humans, he died!
So right now, you have but one choice.
Well, it's not much of a choice really. Your friend is going to die and you're coming to the Fishman District with me.
Horty Jones, the captain of the new Fishman Pirates, is expecting you, and he doesn't like to wait.
That's enough!
Hey, who cares about some stupid rule in the first place? You don't have to listen to this thug! There's someone's life on the line here!
We'll do anything it takes to repay you! Now is not the time to get stuck on pride!
What? Would you give it up already?
Kimmy!
Come along, straw hat!
Now, second gear!
I'll take you by force if I have to!
Troll!
I'm not joining your stupid crew!
I already told you, didn't I?
John Pesso!
Leave us alone!
Get away! The thing is too big!
My word, he made quick work of them.
It just gave up! I guess Luffy can tame sea monsters now?
What happened? That was crazy!
Impressive.
Luffy-chan, up here!
Bring Sanji-chan up here! We'll go back to town!
The Ryugu is moving.
There's lots of humans there, so we might be able to find a blood donor! Let's hurry!
I'm coming!
Cool! Ready to go! Thanks, Kimmy!
Sure! We need to head over to town. Is that okay?
Mason!
Hey! You can't do that! It belongs to the princess!
I'm sorry, guys! We'll bring your ship back as soon as we save Sanji-chan!
And away they go! How are we supposed to get home now? So-la-ti-do!
Hmph!
It's not fair. I'd do anything in the world to save his life, but I don't have the right-
Oh, how are we supposed to get home now, so la-ti-do?
It's not fair. I'd do anything in the world to save his life, but I don't have the right blood type.
No, it's nothing for you to feel bad about.
If he wasn't such a perv, this wouldn't have happened in the first place.
Look at him. He's dying, and he's still thinking about boobs.
So bouncy. So soft and bouncy and so soft and bouncy.
Stop! You're in a delicate state! If you keep thinking about dirty stuff, you're going to lose what little blood you have left!
We may be friends, but considering the way you and Hachi got treated back on Saba-Odi, I should have guessed something like this would happen.
There's some deep-rooted stuff going on here.
Yeah, and to be honest, I don't know how this will go. There's no promise anyone will help us back in town.
We're counting on human donors for blood, but I haven't seen any at all this past month.
In fact, your ship is the first one we've had in a long time.
Why? I thought everyone had to come through here.
Yeah, it wasn't like this before.
Nobody can say for certain, but we think someone's attacking the travelers, like what happened with you guys.
There's something going on in this kingdom, and I have a sinking feeling it's about to get ugly.
Please, ladies, you must be forthright.
Why did you try to conceal those pirates from us?
We're sorry, Prince. They aren't bad people.
It sounds like what happened wasn't their fault.
They're Kami's friends, and they got split up from their crew, so we didn't want them to be thrown in jail as soon as they got here.
Don't be sad!
I hope they find a donor for Sanji.
Alas, you misunderstood us.
Their method of entry is no concern.
They're quite famous.
It would only be a small formality.
We don't consider them enemies, after all.
Yeah, we had different business with them.
Re mi fa sol la ti!
Then this is all our fault.
We had a message to pass on to them, from Jinbei.
Sanji's love for mermaids has turned from a harmless obsession into a life-threatening disaster.
Luffy and his friends take him to the Mermaid Cafe to rest, but they must find a blood donor soon.
Later, Kami introduces them to Madam Charlie, owner of the cafe and expert fortune teller.
Unfortunately, it seems that she only sees destruction in Luffy's future.
On the next, One Piece, the Fishman Island will be annihilated!
Charlie's prophecy!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!